Guide to the Robert Fitzgerald Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Financial and Legal Records, 1927-1985; Series IV; 5; (12 boxes)
  Series IV, Financial and Legal Records, is organized into eleven subseries: Banking, Bills and Receipts, Contracts, Copyright Registration, Insurance, Loans, Material Relating to Nora M. Fitzgerald and Edward J. Fitzgerald Estates, Real Estate, Royalty Statements, Tax Documents, and Other Material.
  - BANKING
    - American National Bank of Amarillo
      - Cancelled checks, 1957-66 (Box 79, Folder 2852-2855)
      - Statements, 1957-66 (Box 79, Folder 2856-2859)
      - Other documents, 1957-66, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2860)
    - Banca Nazionale del Lavoro
      - Check stubs, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2861)
      - Statements and receipts, 1964-74, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2862-2863)
      - Other documents, 1972, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2864)
    - Bank for Savings in the City of New York
      - Account book page, 1959 Jul 9 (Box 79, Folder 2865)
    - Barclays Bank
      - Cancelled checks, 1932 (Box 79, Folder 2866)
      - Statements, 1932 (Box 79, Folder 2867)
    - Cambridge Savings Bank
      - Miscellaneous documents, 1973-74 (Box 79, Folder 2868)
    - Cambridge Trust Company
      - Cancelled checks, 1965-66 (Box 79, Folder 2869-2872)
      - Cancelled checks, 1969-74 (Box 80, Folder 2873-2879)
      - Cancelled checks, 1977-78 (Box 80, Folder 2880-2886)
      - Cancelled checks, 1978-79 (Box 81, Folder 2887-2894)
      - Cancelled checks, 1980 (Box 81, Folder 2895-2898)
      - Check stubs, 1965-80 (Box 82, Folder 2899-2904)
      - Printed ephemera, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 2905)
      - Savings book, 1977-80 (Box 82, Folder 2906)
      - Statements, 1965-73 (Box 82, Folder 2907-2908)
      - Statements, 1974-80 (Box 83, Folder 2909-2913)
      - Other documents, 1965-83, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 2914-2921)
    - Cassa di Risparmio della Spezia
      - Check stubs, 1957-59 (Box 83, Folder 2922)
      - Register, 1958-59 (Box 83, Folder 2923)
    - Central Hanover Bank and Trust Company
      - Miscellaneous documents, 1949, 1951 (Box 83, Folder 2924)
    - Charter Bank of Gainesville
      - Cancelled checks, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 2925)
      - Check register, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 2926)
      - Statements, 1975 (Box 83, Folder 2927)
      - Other documents, 1975, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 2928)
    - Connecticut Bank and Trust Co.
      - Cancelled checks, 1978-82 (Box 84, Folder 2929-2933)
      - Statements, 1979-80 (Box 84, Folder 2934-2936)
      - Other documents, 1979-83 (Box 84, Folder 2937)
    - Credito Italiano
      - Check stubs, 1959-61 (Box 84, Folder 2938-2940)
      - Statements and receipts, 1959-65 (Box 84, Folder 2941-2942)
      - Other documents, 1959-60 (Box 84, Folder 2943)
    - Emigrant Industrial Savings Bank
      - Savings books, 1938-51 (Box 84, Folder 2944)
    - Hampshire National Bank of South Hadley
      - Cancelled checks, 1964, n.d. (Box 84, Folder 2945)
      - Statements, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 2946)
    - The Hanover Bank
      - Cancelled checks, 1955-60 (Box 85, Folder 2947-2952)
      - Check ledger, 1959-60 (Box 85, Folder 2953)
      - Check stubs, 1958-60 (Box 85, Folder 2954)
      - Statements, 1955-60 (Box 85, Folder 2955-2960)
      - Other documents, 1957-60, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2961-2965)
    - Harvard Trust Company
      - Cancelled checks, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 2966)
      - Statements, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 2967)
      - Other documents, n.d. (Box 85, Folder 2968)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust Company
      - Cancelled checks, 1964-73 (Box 86, Folder 2969-2970)
      - Check stubs, 1964-66 (Box 86, Folder 2971)
      - Statements, 1964-66 (Box 86, Folder 2972)
      - Other documents, 1965-73 (Box 86, Folder 2973)
    - Northeast National Bank
      - Miscellaneous documents, 1973 Jun 1 (Box 86, Folder 2974)
    - Unidentified
      - Miscellaneous documents, 1975, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2975)
  - BILLS AND RECEIPTS
    - A. Hermansdorfer & Son, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2976)
    - B. D. Gross & Company, 1971-75 (Box 86, Folder 2977)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield, 1976-80 (Box 86, Folder 2978)
    - Cambridge Electric Light Company, 1964-80 (Box 86, Folder 2979)
    - Cambridge Gas Company, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 2980)
    - Cambridge (Mass.), 1971-83, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2981)
    - Connecticut Blue Cross, Inc., 1956-60 (Box 86, Folder 2982)
    - Embassy Rub & Upholstery Cleaning Co., Inc., 1977-78 (Box 86, Folder 2983)
    - Ente Nazionale per l'Energia Elettrica Compartimento di Roma, 1964-74 (Box 86, Folder 2984)
    - Esercizio Toascana Gas, 1959-61 (Box 86, Folder 2985)
    - Esttatoria Comunale di Perugia, 1965-74, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2986)
    - Fiat (Firm), 1957-59 (Box 86, Folder 2987)
    - Ford Foundation, 1959, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2988)
    - [Fortini's?] Service Station, 1971-72 (Box 86, Folder 2989)
    - George A. Stretton Insurance, 1941-42 (Box 86, Folder 2990)
    - Harvard Club of New York City, 1975-80 (Box 86, Folder 2991)
    - Harvard University. Real Estate Office, 1975-78 (Box 86, Folder 2992)
    - Hayden Stone Inc., 1973 (Box 86, Folder 2993)
    - John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1981-82 (Box 86, Folder 2994)
    - Jordan Marsh Company, 1966, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2995)
    - Medicare, 1976-83 (Box 86, Folder 2996)
    - Munro Smith Insurance, 1942-44 (Box 86, Folder 2997)
    - Nassau Inn, 1977-78 (Box 86, Folder 2998)
    - New England Telephone & Telegraph Company, 1964, n.d. (Box 86, Folder 2999)
    - The New Republic, 1975-78 (Box 86, Folder 3000)
    - The New Yorker, 1956-75 (Box 86, Folder 3001)
    - The Pease Company, 1949 (Box 86, Folder 3002)
    - Ropes & Gray, 1974-82 (Box 86, Folder 3003)
    - Società Elettrica Selt-Valdarno, 1959-61 (Box 86, Folder 3004)
    - Società Italiana per L'Espercizio Telefonico, 1972-74 (Box 86, Folder 3005)
    - Società Telefonica Tirrena, 1959-60 (Box 86, Folder 3006)
    - Southern Bell, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 3007)
    - Ted's Cleaners, 1981 Jun 8 (Box 86, Folder 3008)
    - Yale University, 1976-83 (Box 86, Folder 3009)
    - Others, 1927-75 (Box 86, Folder 3010-3013)
    - Others, 1976-84, n.d. (Box 87, Folder 3014-3016)
  - CONTRACTS
    - Doubleday and Company, Inc., 1953, 1965
    - Harcourt, Brace and Company, 1936-47 (Box 87, Folder 3017)
    - Houghton Mifflin and Company, 1962 Apr 24 (Box 87, Folder 3018)
    - New Directions, 1971, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 3019)
    - Northeastern University Press, 1983 Jul 5 (Box 87, Folder 3020)
    - Random House (Firm) (Box 87, Folder 3021)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1979 Jan 18 (Box 87, Folder 3022)
  - COPYRIGHT REGISTRATION
    - Poems, 1935 Nov 21 (Box 87, Folder 3023)
    - The Third Kind of Knowledge, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 3024)
    - A Wreath for the Sea, 1943-44 (Box 87, Folder 3025)
  - INCOME AND OTHER STATEMENTS
    - Bank of the Southwest, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 3026)
    - Cash Equivalent Fund, Inc., 1980-83 (Box 87, Folder 3027)
    - Connecticut Savings Bank, 1978 Jul 78 (Box 87, Folder 3028)
    - Financial Programs Inc., 1973 (Box 87, Folder 3029)
    - Hardee's Building, 1979-80 (Box 87, Folder 3030)
    - Harvard University, 1966-81 (Box 87, Folder 3031)
    - Harvard University. Employee Credit Union, 1972-78 (Box 87, Folder 3032)
    - Harvard University Retirement Plan, 1965-81 (Box 87, Folder 3033-3034)
    - Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner & Smith, Inc., 1981, n.d. (Box 87, Folder 3035)
    - Moseley, Hallgarten, Estabrook & Weeden Inc., 1980-82 (Box 87, Folder 3036)
    - New England Merchants National Bank, 1973 May 21 (Box 87, Folder 3037)
    - Princeton University, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 3038)
    - "Saturday Club", 1984 (Box 87, Folder 3039)
    - University of Florida, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 3040)
  - INSURANCE
    - Harvard University
      - Aetna Insurance Company, 1969-75 (Box 87, Folder 3041)
      - Aetna Life Insurance Company, 1965-77 (Box 87, Folder 3042)
      - John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1979-80 (Box 87, Folder 3043)
      - Prudential Insurance Company of America, 1981, n.d. (Box 87, Folder 3044)
    - Other Policies
      - Allstate Insurance Company, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 3045)
      - Boston Insurance Group, 1966-67 (Box 87, Folder 3046)
      - Colonial Penn Franklin Insurance Company, 1977-79, n.d. (Box 87, Folder 3047)
      - Ellis & Andrews, 1966 Feb 21 (Box 87, Folder 3048)
      - National Casualty Company, 1966 Feb 14 (Box 87, Folder 3049)
      - Phoenix Insurance Company (Hartford, Conn.), 1958 (Box 87, Folder 3050)
      - Societa Assicuratrice Industriale, 1968-72 (Box 87, Folder 3051)
      - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, 1951-52 (Box 87, Folder 3052)
      - United States. Veterans' Administration, 1943 (Box 87, Folder 3053)
  - LOANS
    - [Harvard University. Employee Credit Union?] disclosure statement, 1970 Apr 9 (Box 87, Folder 3054)
    - Harvard University faculty mortgage loan, 1966, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 3055)
    - Installment note [for] education loan to employee, 1969-74 (Box 87, Folder 3056)
    - Stamford Federal Savings and Loan Association, 1946-53 (Box 87, Folder 3057)
  - MATERIAL RELATING TO FITZGERALD ESTATES
    - Application for the Appointment of Successor Trustee, [1944?] (Box 88, Folder 3058)
    - Correspondence (copies), 1944-76 (Box 88, Folder 3059)
    - [Legal] Notices, 1973-79 (Box 88, Folder 3060)
    - Memorandum of Conversation (2 copies), 1978 Aug 7 (Box 88, Folder 3061)
    - Petition for Authority to Borrow Funds and Execute Mortgage, and to Execute New Lease, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 3062)
    - Reports, 1935, 1944 (Box 88, Folder 3063)
    - Schedule of Taxable Income, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 3064)
    - Summary of Audit, [1944?] (Box 88, Folder 3065)
    - Summary Notes [on] Meeting, 1977 Aug 10 (Box 88, Folder 3066)
    - Trust statements, 1950-79 (Box 88, Folder 3067)
    - Other documents, 1931-56, n.d. (Box 88, Folder 3068)
  - REAL ESTATE
    - 14 Fernald Drive, Cambridge, Mass., 1975-81 (Box 88, Folder 3069)
    - 20 Bryant Street, Cambridge, Mass., 1965-73 (Box 88, Folder 3070)
    - 70 Acres Road, Redding, Conn., 1949, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 3071)
    - 77 Raymond Street, Cambridge, Mass., 1964 Mar 13 (Box 88, Folder 3072)
    - 127 Bayard Lane, Princeton, N.J., 1977 Jul 13 (Box 88, Folder 3073)
    - 408 Gordon Glen Manor, Gainesville, Fl. (Box 88, Folder 3074)
    - 6812 48 Ave. No., 1970 (Box 88, Folder 3075)
    - Franklin Street, Vineyard Haven, Mass., 1981 May 7 (Box 88, Folder 3076)
  - ROYALTY STATEMENTS
    - Doubleday & Company, Inc., 1961-83 (Box 88, Folder 3077-3081)
    - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, 1969-81 (Box 88, Folder 3082)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1936-77 (Box 88, Folder 3083-3086)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1978-84 (Box 89, Folder 3087-3088)
    - Harold Matson Company, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 3089)
    - Houghton Mifflin and Company, 1966 Mar 31 (Box 89, Folder 3090)
    - MacMillan Company, 1967-78 (Box 89, Folder 3091)
    - New Directions Publishing Corp., 1956-83, n.d. (Box 89, Folder 3092-3093)
    - Randon House (Firm), 1983-84 (Box 89, Folder 3094)
  - TAX DOCUMENTS
    - 1936-1946, 1937-47 (Box 89, Folder 3095)
    - 1947-1950, 1948-51 (Box 89, Folder 3096)
    - 1951, 1951-52 (Box 89, Folder 3097)
    - 1952, 1952-53 (Box 89, Folder 3098)
    - 1953, 1953-54 (Box 89, Folder 3099)
    - 1954, 1954-55 (Box 89, Folder 3100)
    - 1955, 1956 (Box 89, Folder 3101)
    - 1956, 1956-57 (Box 89, Folder 3102)
    - 1957, 1957-58 (Box 89, Folder 3103)
    - 1958, 1958-59 (Box 89, Folder 3104)
    - 1959, 1959-60 (Box 89, Folder 3105)
    - 1966, 1965-67 (Box 89, Folder 3106)
      Includes receipts
    - 1967 (Box 89, Folder 3107)
    - 1968, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 3108)
    - 1969, 1969-70 (Box 89, Folder 3109)
    - 1969, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 3110)
      Tax documents for Mrs. Verna Johnson Morgan
    - 1970, 1971 Mar 23 (Box 89, Folder 3111)
    - 1971, 1971-72 (Box 89, Folder 3112)
    - 1972, 1973 (Box 89, Folder 3113)
    - 1973, 1974 (Box 89, Folder 3114)
    - 1974, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 3115)
    - 1975, 1976 (Box 89, Folder 3116)
    - 1976, 1976-77 (Box 89, Folder 3117)
    - 1977, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 3118)
    - 1978, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 3119)
    - 1979, 1979-80 (Box 90, Folder 3120)
    - 1980, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 3121)
    - 1981-83, 1982-83 (Box 90, Folder 3122)
  - OTHER
    - Affadavit of Witnesses to Revocation of Will, 1946 May 16 (Box 90, Folder 3123)
    - Agreement between Eleanor Green Fitzgerald and Robert Stuart Fitzgerald, 1946 May 25 (Box 90, Folder 3124)
    - Certificate of Marriage, 1935 Dec 24 (Box 90, Folder 3125)
    - Certificate of Marriage, 1947 Apr 20 (Box 90, Folder 3126)
    - Certification of Birth, 1944 Mar 24 (Box 90, Folder 3127)
    - Copy of Account Kept by Edward J. Fitzgerald, 1929-31 (Box 90, Folder 3128)
    - Discharge of Mortgage, 1966 Feb 2 (Box 90, Folder 3129)
    - Divorce degree, 1946 Jun 12 (Box 90, Folder 3130)
    - Financial aid application, [1970?] (Box 90, Folder 3131)
    - Indenture of Trust, 1967-74 (Box 90, Folder 3132)
    - Last Will and Testament, 1931-75 (Box 90, Folder 3133-3134)
    - [Loose notes], 1951-83, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 3135)
    - "Pitfalls to Watch for in Planning Your Estate," interview, reprint, U.S. News and World Report, 1973 Oct (Box 90, Folder 3136)
    - Power of Attorney form, 1931 Oct 14 (Box 90, Folder 3137)
    - Quit-Claim Deed, 1941 Mar 13 (Box 90, Folder 3138)
    - Social Security documents, 1975-84, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 3139-3140)
    - Stock certificate, 1953 Apr 2 (Box 90, Folder 3141)
    - Warranty Deed, 1948 Aug 9 (Box 90, Folder 3142)
- Personal Papers, 1892-1985; Series V; 7.92; (19 boxes)
  Series V, Personal Papers is organized into fourteen subseries: Artwork, Clippings, Family Papers, Material Relating to Time Magazine, Medical Records, Military Records, Notes and Notebooks, Photographs, Printed Ephemera, Real Estate, School Records, Speaking Engagments, Teaching and Course Material, and Other Material.
  - ARTWORK
    - By Robert Fitzgerald
      - Drawings and watercolors, 1946-47, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3143-3144)
    - By Other People
      - [Chase?], Beka, 1968, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3145)
      - Fitzgerald, Sarah, 1947, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3146)
      - Larsson, Rayomnd E. F., 1948 (Box 91, Folder 3147)
      - McGarrell, [James?], n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3148)
      - Zabel, Fernando, 1961 Mar 22 (Box 91, Folder 3149)
      - Unidentified, 1978, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3150)
  - CLIPPINGS
    - About Robert Fitzgerald
      - General interest articles and brief mentions, 1923-84, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3151-3152)
    - About Other People
      - Abramowicz, Janet, 1980, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3153)
      - Ackerley, J. J. (Joe Randolph), 1969 Mar 27
      - Agee, James, 1966-84, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3154)
      - Alfred, William, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 3155)
      - Auden, W. H. (Wystan Hugh), 1969, 1972 (Box 91, Folder 3156)
      - Bacon, Helen, 1979 Jun 10 (Box 91, Folder 3157)
      - Beattie, Ann, 1980 Jun (Box 91, Folder 3158)
      - Beckett, Samuel, 1983, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3159)
      - Brooks, John R., 1981 Mar 27 (Box 91, Folder 3160)
      - Brower, Reuben Arthur, 1975 Mar 29 (Box 91, Folder 3161)
      - Bulter of Saffron Walden, Richard, 1982 Mar 10 (Box 91, Folder 3162)
      - Dyer-Bennett, Richard, 1978-79, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3163)
      - Eliot, T. S., 1965 (Box 91, Folder 3164)
      - Evans, Walker, 1975-78, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3165)
      - Farrell, Patric, 1966, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3166)
      - Field, Edward, 1980 Oct (Box 91, Folder 3167)
      - Finley, John H. (John Huston), 1974, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3168)
      - Fitts, Dudley, 1954 Jul 11
      - Frohock, Wilbur (Merrill), 1984 Aug 2 (Box 91, Folder 3169)
      - Gellhorn, Martha, 1958 Mar 17 (Box 91, Folder 3170)
      - Gibbs, Walcott, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 3171)
      - Giroux, Robert, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3172)
      - Gordon, Caroline, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3173)
      - Gregory, Horace, 1982 Mar 13 (Box 91, Folder 3174)
      - Guillen, Jorge, 1976, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3175)
      - Hellman, Lillian, 1982-84, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3176)
      - Hemingway, Ernest, 1949-81 (Box 91, Folder 3177)
      - Hoffman, Daniel, 1974 Jun (Box 91, Folder 3178)
      - Huston, John, 1981 Jan (Box 91, Folder 3179)
      - Jakobson, Roman, 1982 Jul 23 (Box 91, Folder 3180)
      - Jones, Howard Mumford, 1981 May 22 (Box 91, Folder 3181)
      - Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1978 May 29
      - Kizer, Carolyn, 1961 Aug 31 (Box 91, Folder 3182)
      - Lattimore, Richmond, 1984 Feb 28 (Box 91, Folder 3183)
      - LeBaron, Charles, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 3184)
      - Lee, Andrea, 1983-84, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3185)
      - Lindsay, Vachel, 1931-61, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3186)
      - Lord, George de Forest, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 3187)
      - Lowell, Robert, 1960-77, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3188)
      - MacDonald, Dwight, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 3189)
      - McKelway, St. Clair, 1980 Jan 28 (Box 91, Folder 3190)
      - MacLeish, Archibald, 1982-83, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3191)
      - Marceau, Marcel, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3192)
      - Matthews, Jackson, 1978 Dec 18 (Box 91, Folder 3193)
      - Matthews, T. S., 1960 Mar 28 (Box 91, Folder 3194)
      - Maxwell, William, 1975, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 3195)
      - Morris, Jan, 1974 Mar 17
      - Nims, John Frederick, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 3196)
      - O'Connor, Flannery, 1957-72, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3197)
      - Parry, J. H. (John Horace), n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3198)
      - Pound, Ezra, 1949-69, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3199)
      - Ricci, Leonardo, n.y. Oct 11 (Box 91, Folder 3200)
      - Rodell, Susanna, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3201)
      - St. John, Clara Seymour, 1958, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3202)
      - Saint-John Perse, 1975 Sep 23 (Box 91, Folder 3203)
      - Santayana, George, 1952 Oct 27 (Box 91, Folder 3204)
      - Shapiro, Karl Jay, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3205)
      - Shore, Jane, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3206)
      - Simpson, Eileen B., 1977-82, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3207)
      - Smith, Alfred Emanuel, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3208)
      - Speaight, Robert, 1976 (Box 91, Folder 3209)
      - Stendahl, Brita K., 1980 Sep (Box 91, Folder 3210)
      - Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1952
      - Thurber, James, 1952, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3211)
      - Ungaretti, Giuseppe, 1970 Mar 14 (Box 91, Folder 3212)
      - Vendler, Helen, 1980 Mar 29 (Box 91, Folder 3213)
      - Warren, Robert Penn, 1984 Dec (Box 91, Folder 3214)
      - Zabel, Morton Dauwen, 1957 Apr 6 (Box 91, Folder 3215)
      - Zaturenska, Marya, 1982 Jan 21 (Box 91, Folder 3216)
      - Others, 1949-80, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 3217)
    - Topics
      - Art and architecture, 1968-80, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3218)
      - Cambridge University
      - Catholicism and religion, 1941-80, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3219)
      - Cinema, 1962-83, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3220)
      - Comic strips/Cartoons, 1964-75, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3221)
      - Education, 1951 Nov (Box 92, Folder 3222)
      - Food and wine, 1977-84, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3223)
      - Harvard University, 1969-83, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3224)
      - Health and medicine, 1976-81, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3225)
      - Literature, 1939-83, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3226)
      - Military matters and World War II, 1940-64, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3227-3228)
      - Publishing, 1959, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 3229)
      - Shady Hill Project, 1966-72 (Box 92, Folder 3230)
      - Springfield, Illinois, 1913-1983, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3231-3232)
      - Theater, 1952-71, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3233)
      - Other subjects, 1931-84, n.d. (Box 92, Folder 3234-3236)
    - Periodicals
      - Commonweal, 1948-56 (Box 92, Folder 3237-3242)
      - The Nation, 1941-50, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3243)
      - The New Republic, 1940-53 (Box 93, Folder 3244)
      - The New Yorker, 1929-84, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3245-3246)
  - FAMILY PAPERS
    - Donn, Nora Anne Stuart
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3247)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3248)
      - Printed ephemera, 1954 Dec 11 (Box 93, Folder 3249)
    - Fitzgerald, Anne M. Stuart
      - Annie & Wilie's Prayer, 1896 (Box 93, Folder 3250)
      - Certified Copy of a Record of Death, 1944 Jun 15 (Box 93, Folder 3251)
      - Checks, 1909, 1913 (Box 93, Folder 3252)
      - Clippings, 1905, 1913 (Box 93, Folder 3253)
      - Diary, 1892 (Box 93, Folder 3254)
      - Massachusetts Mutual Life Insurance Company documents, 1908-12, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3255)
    - Fitzgerald, Arthur
      - Clippings, 1933, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 3256)
      - Sermon Deliverd at the Requiem Mass for Arthur M. Fitzgerald, 1957 Jul 19 (Box 93, Folder 3257)
    - Fitzgerald, Barnaby
      - Artwork, 1959-74, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3258)
      - Cheley Colorado Camps material, 1965-66 (Box 93, Folder 3259)
      - Christmas card, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 3260)
      - Clippings, 1973-83, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3261)
      - Exhibition announcements, 1980-84, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3262)
      - Notebooks, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 3263)
      - Photographs, 1978-79, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3264-3265)
        Includes photographs of Barnaby Fitzgerald and unidentified others
      - Printed ephemera, 1961-83, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3266)
      - School records, 1966-71 (Box 93, Folder 3267)
      - School work, 1966, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3268)
    - Fitzgerald, Benedict
      - Bills and receipts, 1970-78, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3269)
      - Certificate of birth, 1949 Mar 9 (Box 93, Folder 3270)
      - "Chalk," draft, screenplay, typescript, photocopy
        See: Fitzgerald, Michael, Box 94, folder 3306
      - Clippings, 1971-80, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3271)
      - Drawings, 1959, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 3272)
      - Notebook, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3273)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3274)
      - [Poems], drafts, holograph and typescript, 1971-73, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3275)
      - Printed ephemera, 1957-71, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3276)
      - School records, 1966-72 (Box 93, Folder 3277)
      - School work, 1959-68, n.d. (Box 93, Folder 3278)
        Includes letter from Barnaby to Robert Fitzgerald
    - Fitzgerald, Bernard Montague
      - Clippings, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3279)
      - Sangamon Loan and Trust Company savings book, 1914 (Box 94, Folder 3280)
    - Fitzgerald, Caterina
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3281)
      - [Poems], drafts, holograph and typescript, 1964, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3282)
      - Printed ephemera, 1955-64, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3283)
      - School records, 1964-72, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3284)
      - School work and loose notes, 1965, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3285)
      - Stationary, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3286)
    - Fitzgerald, Edward J.
      - Last Will and Testament (Box 94, Folder 3287)
      - Probate court documents, 1966 Apr 13 (Box 94, Folder 3288)
    - Fitzgerald Family
      - Clippings, 1959 Oct (Box 94, Folder 3289)
      - Genealogical notes, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3290)
      - Photographs, 1950-74, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3291)
        Photographs of two or more members of the Fitzgerald family, including Robert, Sarah, and children
    - Fitzgerald, James Michael
      - Bills and receipts, 1906 Sep (Box 94, Folder 3292)
      - Clippings, 1960 Jun 16 (Box 94, Folder 3293)
    - Fitzgerald, Jane
      - Clippings, 1937 Apr 11 (Box 94, Folder 3294)
    - Fitzgerald, Joan
      - Photographs, 1966-78, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3295)
      - Printed ephemera, 1980, n.d. (Box 94, Folder 3296)
    - Fitzgerald, Maria
      - Bills and receipts, 1959-66 (Box 94, Folder 3297)
      - "Experiment with Time," story, printed version, Interzone, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 3298)
      - Photographs, 1958 (Box 94, Folder 3299)
      - [Poems], drafts, typescript, corrected, 1963-66 (Box 94, Folder 3300)
      - Printed ephemera, 1950 May 6 (Box 94, Folder 3301)